export default {
    title: 'States/Capitals of Brazil | State - Capital',
    description: 'The Capitals and states of Brazil',
    cards: [
        {
            front: "Acre",
            back: "Rio Branco"
        },
        {
            front: "Alagoas",
            back: "Maceió"
        },
        {
            front: "Amapá",
            back: "Macapá"
        },
        {
            front: "Amazonas",
            back: "Manaus"
        },
        {
            front: "Bahia",
            back: "Salvador"
        },
        {
            front: "Ceará",
            back: "Fortaleza"
        },
        {
            front: "Distrito Federal",
            back: "Brasília"
        },
        {
            front: "Espírito Santo",
            back: "Vitória"
        },
        {
            front: "Goiás",
            back: "Goiânia"
        },
        {
            front: "Maranhão",
            back: "São Luís"
        },
        {
            front: "Mato Grosso",
            back: "Cuiabá"
        },
        {
            front: "Mato Grosso do Sul",
            back: "Campo Grande"
        },
        {
            front: "Minas Gerais",
            back: "Belo Horizonte"
        },
        {
            front: "Pará",
            back: "Belém"
        },
        {
            front: "Paraíba",
            back: "João Pessoa"
        },
        {
            front: "Paraná",
            back: "Curitiba"
        },
        {
            front: "Pernambuco",
            back: "Recife"
        },
        {
            front: "Piauí",
            back: "Teresina"
        },
        {
            front: "Rio de Janeiro",
            back: "Rio de Janeiro"
        },
        {
            front: "Rio Grande do Norte",
            back: "Natal"
        },
        {
            front: "Rio Grande do Sul",
            back: "Porto Alegre"
        },
        {
            front: "Rondônia",
            back: "Porto Velho"
        },
        {
            front: "Roraima",
            back: "Boa Vista"
        },
        {
            front: "Santa Catarina",
            back: "Florianópolis"
        },
        {
            front: "São Paulo",
            back: "São Paulo"
        },
        {
            front: "Sergipe",
            back: "Aracaju"
        },
        {
            front: "Tocantins",
            back: "Palmas"
        },
    ]
};
